A Guide to the Records from the School Health Nurses, Arlington Public Schools, 1934-1991
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Transfer of School Nurses from the Department of Education to Department of Human Resources
  - Staff Analysis--School Health Services, Arlington Public Schools, December 1, 1967 (Box 14)
  - School Health Services, Norfolk, Virginia, 1966-1973 (Box 14)
  - School Health Services, Richmond Public Schools, May 1969 (Box 14)
  - Arlington County Board's Advisory Committee on Health and Welfare, 1966-1971 (Box 14)
  - Merger, 1971-1973 (Box 14)
  - Transfer of Nurses, 1969-1973 (Box 14)
  - Transfer of Nurses, Research Materials, 1971-1973 (Box 15)
  - Transfer of Nurses, Research Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - School Health Transfer, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Problems for Concern Regarding Possible Transfer of School Nurses to Department of Human Resources, February 16, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Transfer of School Nurses to Department of Human Resources, May-June 1973 (Box 15)
  - Considerations Regarding Proposed Merger of School Health with Department of Human Resources, June 4, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Memorandum to the School Board from Robert L. Chisholm, Superintendent, on School Health Services, June 5, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Negotiations with the County Board Regarding Terms and Conditions of Employment, July 1973 (Box 15)
  - Report to the Arlington County Board on Proposed Transfer of School Health Services, from Michael Timpane, Chairman, Arlington School Board, July 6, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Clerk's Notes of Proceedings, Regular County Board Meeting, July 11, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Committee on School Health Services, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - Department of Human Resources - Pay Transfer, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
  - 1973 Agreement between School Board and County Board, Status as of August 1983 (Box 15)
  - Consolidation of School Health Nurses with Public Health Nurses, 1980 1980-1983 (Box 15)
  - Class and Comp Transition Rule Adjustment, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
  - Public Health Nursing Materials (Box 15)
- Photographs
  - Picture Portrayal of the School Health Program (Box 15)
  - [Retirement Party], no date (Box 15)
  - [Events], no date (Box 15)
  - [Event], no date (Box 15)
  - Photographs of School Health and Flood (Box 15)
  - Hoffman-Boston Clinic (Box 15)
  - TMC-Arlington County Public Schools (Box 15)
  - Swanson Clinic, Thelma Hill (Box 15)
  - [Holiday Party and Group Pictures of Nurses, July 1950] (Box 15)
  - [Event] (Box 15)
  - School Health 1964 (Box 15)
  - Fall 1968 (Box 15)
  - Dr. Hughes, School Health, From Gunston, TB Testing, November 1969 (Box 15)
  - Our Own Hospital Book, [1982] (Box 15)
  - Negatives, not associated with any photographs in the collection; envelope labeled "1/62- latest of Boat & Xmas Apt. pictures" (Box 15)